<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Experiences on Batjaa&#39;s corner</title>
    <link>/experiences/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Experiences on Batjaa&#39;s corner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 19:29:17 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/experiences/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quartzy, Inc</title>
      <link>/experiences/quartzy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/experiences/quartzy/</guid>
      <description>Separated and rebuilt the frontend application in EmberJS for quartzy.com. Developing end to end features that expands through multiple internal products communicating through RPC. Maintains and integrates 3rd party tools and platforms for sales and marketing teams. Redesigned client managing admin panel application while working and managing contractors. Rebuilt the internal catalog uploading module to allow big files to be uploaded which helped the data analysis team to not be depended on engineers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fieldbook, Inc</title>
      <link>/experiences/fieldbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/experiences/fieldbook/</guid>
      <description> Responsible for product development, including implementing requested features and fixing bugs.
 Fixed several bugs which were causing double requests to be sent and cut down load time by 2x.
 Successfully implemented a worker node for processing sheets offline removed several timeout exceptions.
 Improved test stability which had become a headache for shipment by combining several promise libraries and refactoring realtime test code.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orbit Systems, Inc</title>
      <link>/experiences/orbit-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/experiences/orbit-systems/</guid>
      <description> Developed a cross-browser compatible Project Management Web application. 5x faster than the previous version and has a more friendly user interface with great user experience in mind. Using JEE, Spring framework and Hibernate with Oracle Database in backend Supports real-time updates using WebSockets.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-Employed</title>
      <link>/experiences/self-employed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 19:29:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/experiences/self-employed/</guid>
      <description>Designed, developed, and deployed a nationwide Railway Monitoring system using C#, providing efficient solution to share workspace between server-client and data manipulation for better storage. Designed and developed a Loan management system using C# which supports multiple companies loans and different asset types. Designed and developed a stock trading platform in C# while handling full stock portfolio management and numerous calculations of stock market indicators. It uses Java web crawler for tracking stock price.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>